<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidMobile</string>
    <string name="tie_username">Username</string>
    <string name="tie_email">Email</string>
    <string name="tie_password">Password</string>
    <string name="alternative_login">Or connect with</string>
    <string name="write_file">This app needs access to your file storage so that it can write files.</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>s

    <string name="classics_genre">Classic literature is a term most readers are probably familiar with. The term covers a much wider array of works than classical literature. Older books that
        retain their popularity are almost always considered to be among the classics. This means that the ancient Greek and Roman authors of classical literature fall into this category as well.
        It\'s not just age that makes a book a classic, however. Books that have a timeless quality are considered to be in this category. While determining if
        a book is well-written or not is a subjective endeavor, it is generally agreed
        that classics have high-quality prose.  </string>

    <string name="romance_genre">Novels of this type of genre fiction place their primary focus on the relationship and romantic love between two people, and must have an "emotionally satisfying
        and optimistic ending." There are many subgenres of the romance novel, including fantasy, historical romance, paranormal fiction, and science fiction</string>
    <string name="fiction_genre">Fiction refers to literature created from the imagination. Mysteries, science fiction, romance, fantasy, chick lit, crime thrillers are all fiction genres.
        Whether or not all of these genres should be considered “literature” is a matter of opinion. Some of these fiction genres are taught in literature classrooms and some are not usually taught,
        considered more to be reading for entertainment. Works often taught in literature classrooms are referred to as “literary fiction” including
        classics by Dickens, Austen, Twain, and Poe, for example.</string>

    <string name="nonfiction_genre">Like fiction, non-fiction also has a sub-genre called “literary nonfiction” that refers to literature based on fact but written in creative way,
        making it as enjoyable to read as fiction. Of course there are MANY other types of nonfiction such as cook books, fitness articles, crafting manuals, etc. which are not “literature,”
        meaning not the types of works we would study in a literature classroom. However, you may not be aware of the many types of nonfiction we would study, such as biography,
        memoir or autobiography, essays, speeches, and humor. Of these literary nonfiction genres, they can be long like a book or series of books or short like an essay or journal entry.
        Some examples of these you are already familiar with, like The Diary of Anne Frank or Angela’s Ashes by Frank McCourt.
        These works of literary nonfiction have character, setting, plot, conflict, figurative language, and theme just like literary fiction.</string>

    <string name="science_genre">Science fiction is a genre of fiction in which the stories often
tell about science and technology of the future. It is
important to note that science fiction has a relationship with
the principles of science—these stories involve partially truepartially fictitious laws or theories of science. It should not be
completely unbelievable, because it then ventures into the
genre fantasy.
The plot creates situations different from those of both the
present day and the known past. Science fiction texts also
include a human element, explaining what effect new
discoveries, happenings and scientific developments will have
on us in the future. </string>

    <string name="inspirational_genre">The genre of “religious, inspirational, and spiritual” encompasses a diverse collection of material that includes both fiction
        and nonfiction books covering a wide range of religions, from Christianity to Buddhism to Wiccan. Books may be associated with one
        specific religion, or may be more general, but they often focus on an inspirational theme with underlying religious lessons or ethics.
This genre also includes books that cover topics meant to encourage spiritual growth, but are not necessarily tied to one religion. Books that offer
        techniques for improving physical health, emotional well-being, and personal relationships are popular in this genre, especially when they pull
        from concepts and practices from all over the world.</string>
</resources>
